http://www.danielpearl.org/misc/privacy/

Introduction
The site editor takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as “data” below) that may be collected by this site. This policy does not apply to other entities that are not owned or controlled by the site editor, nor does it apply to persons that are not employees or agents of the site editor, or that are not under the site editor’s control. Please take time to read this site’s Terms of Service.
Collection of Data
As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor’s policy to display advertising) is set forth below. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to.
Use of Data
Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your data being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor’s policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by the site editor to protect the site editor’s legal rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites.
Cookies
Like many web sites, this web site sets and uses cookies to enhance your user experience — to remember your personal settings, for instance. Advertisements are not currently used, but may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site’s cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative if you want to find out more information about this practice.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. This web site does not collect sensitive information such as credit card numbers or social security numbers. This web site does not use encryption or SSL and users should be aware that it is possible for information submitted to be intercepted by other parties.
Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that NCN is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Email Newsletter
We send our email newsletter to those users who have signed up to be on our mailing list. Every mass email from us sent by CoolerEmail contains an option for the user to unsubscribe.
Affiliated Services
We offer some of our services on or through other web sites such as Google. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Google in order to deliver the service. We may combine the information you submit with information from other Google services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our site. We process such information under this Privacy Policy.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. You will be notified of substantial changes to this policy either by through the posting of a prominent announcement on the site, and/or by a mail message sent to any e-mail address you have provided.
NO GUARANTEES
While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, the site editor is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor’s control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, the site editor offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact the site administrator.
Search for:
Join Us on Facebook
Connect on Twitter Tweets by @DanielPearlFNDN
Video
Join Us
ABOUT DANIEL PEARL FOUNDATION The Daniel Pearl Foundation was formed in 2002 in memory of the Wall Street Journal's South Asia Bureau Chief, journalist/musician Daniel Pearl, to promote the ideals that inspired his life and work. The Foundation works domestically and internationally to promote cross-cultural dialogue and understanding, to counter cultural and religious intolerance, to cultivate responsible and balanced journalism, and to inspire unity and friendship through music.
LOOKING FOR SOMETHING?
Search for:
